https://www.hooked-on-rc-airplanes.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy for Hooked on RC Airplanes
We recognize that your privacy is important. This document
outlines the types of personal information we receive and
collect when you use www.hooked-on-rc-airplanes.com, as well as some
of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this
will help you make an informed decision about sharing
personal information with us.
www.hooked-on-rc-airplanes.com strives to maintain the highest
standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our
operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our
customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our
website.
Personal Information
www.hooked-on-rc-airplanes.com collects personally identifiable
information from the visitors to our website only on a
voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a
voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email
address, company name and telephone number.
This information is collected if you request information
from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign
up to join our email list or request some other service or
information from us. The information collected is internally
reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify
our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.
Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in
our files. If we make material changes in the collection of
personally identifiable information we will inform you by
placing a notice on our site. Personal information received
from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and
will not be sold or provided to third parties.
Use of Cookies and Web Beacons
We may use cookies to help you personalize your online
experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to
your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to
enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of
a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to
a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites
pages, or register with any of our site's services, a cookie
enables www.hooked-on-rc-airplanes.com to recall your specific
information on subsequent visits.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by
modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to
decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the
interactive features of the site.
A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor
your journey around a single website or collection of sites.
They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used
by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic.
They may be used in association with cookies to understand
how visitors interact with the pages and content on the
pages of a web site.
We may serve third party advertisements that use cookies and
web beacons in the course of ads being served on our web
site to ascertain how many times you've seen an
advertisement. No personally identifiable information you
give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so
they cannot personally identify you with that information on
our web site.
Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google,
which uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google uses the
DART cookie, which enables it to serve ads to our users based
on their visits to this site and other sites on the Web. You
may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the
Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify
you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be
used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions
shouldn't cause a problem with our site, should you so
choose.
Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal
information from anyone under 13 years of age.
site and to gather demographic information about our user
base as a whole.
The information collected is used solely
for internal review and not shared with other organizations
for commercial purposes.
Release of Information
If www.hooked-on-rc-airplanes.com is sold, the information we have
obtained from you through your voluntary participation in
our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale
in order that the service being provided to you may
continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our
website of that change in control and practices, and we will
make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors
any opt-out requests you might make of us.
How You Can Correct or Remove Information
We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our
commitment to protect your personal information. If you have
submitted personal information through our website and would
like that information deleted from our records or would like
to update or correct that information, please use our Contact Us page.
Updates and Effective Date
www.hooked-on-rc-airplanes.com reserves the right to make changes in
this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy
practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy
practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy
policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy
so that you will know what information we collect and how we
use it.
Agreeing to Terms
If you do not agree to www.hooked-on-rc-airplanes.com's Privacy
Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use
this site or any services offered by this site.
Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy
policy.
HomeNew Pages!RC Plane ForumThe BasicsHow to Fly RCRadio BasicsPopular TrainersFlight SimulatorsBuilding RC PlanesRC Plane TypesRC AerobaticsPowerNitro RC EnginesElectric PlanesBrushless MotorsLipo Battery PacksPropeller SelectionAirplanes TypesRC GlidersSport AirplanesScale RC AirplanesRC JetsAmphibious PlanesTop BrandsParkZone AirplanesHobby ZoneOther Cool StuffRC QuadcoptersUAV DronesAerial PhotographyVideo GogglesWatch VideosAbout MeContact Me!Affordable DRONE
Hooked on RC Airplanes!
By Matt Brown, Copyright © 2007-2020 Hooked-on-RC-Airplanes.com
